CONTACT ME AT

• Melbourne, Victoria

srisainee2310@gmail.com

littlebravesri.github.io

in linkedin.com/in/sri-saineethirumurugan/

EDUCATION

- Master of Data Science | RMIT University
- Bachelor of Computer Science and Engineering | Anna University

SKILLS SUMMARY

- •••• Python
- •••• SQL
- •••• Machine Learning
- •••• Java
- •••• R
- ●●●● Data Analysis
- ••• Data Visualization
- •••• Azure

SRI SAINEE THIRUMURUGAN

DATA SCIENTIST

PERSONAL PROFILE

Master of Data Science student having well developed teamwork, communication and problem-solving skills broadened during academic experience. Possessing extensive knowledge in Python, SQL, Azure and OOPs through experience in projects. Confident about actively engaging in a dynamic and challenging environment to develop personal growth while contributing to the organization's success.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Data Analyst Internship

Wings Cyberspcae International | April 2021 - July 2021

- Experimented different web scraping tools to extract eBay product details including Category, Subcategory etc. using BeautifulSoup, Scrapy, ParseHub and Octoparse.
- Studied Elasticsearch and how to upload data into Elasticsearch.
- Created dashboards using Kibana, Tableau and PowerBI with extracted eBay product details.

Team Member

Know your terms | November 2020 - January 2021

- Worked in an Agile environment.
- Extracted text from web pages using Beautiful Soup and Scrapy.
- Mined text from PDF and Docx files for displaying relevant terms and conditions for the users.

Data Science and Analytics Internship

The Sparks Foundation | October 2020 - October 2020

- Developed dashboard using PowerBI to perform Exploratory Data Analysis.
- Performed Business Analysis using range of graphs and plots.
- Developed storyboard using Tableau to perform Time Series Analysis on COVID-19.
- Built interactive and animated visualizations to analyse the COVID data.
- Performed storytelling by interactive graphs enabling easy analysis.